Nitrna.
I am Aika Ki-nuri from Scene On.
This will be a game project following the last one.
Please give me your best regards.
Now, what game are we going to try today?
Oh!
Air!
ASMR! Oh! I think I may have heard it for the first time. It's the first time I've heard it.
Well, let me explain the rules. The person who gives a question draws a subject from the nighttime kun and only you look at it.
You have to say what is written on the subject, like "boa" or "kakjian!
Jaka-jaan! and so on.
I don't do it, but it is air ASMR because I express only with sounds. I see.
I see.
The person who answers should listen to the sound and guess what the subject is.
Let's try to get at least 3 correct answers in a minute!
But that's less than before. From last time.
That's right.
Three is quite a lot.
But they said it was difficult.
I hope you've already tied it up. Definitely make it the last time.
That's all it is, isn't it?
What should I do?
I don't know what the subject is, so it could be really mean.
Juice-Juice's Corner
Let's start the one-minute air ASMR.
Dooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo, no eyes
I see... I see... no... that's dangerous.
No, it's not dangerous.
What was that?
we've got one pass without even using it, and it's only one pass...
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Wait, wait, wait!
Next, next, next...
Next, next, next!
It's the third one!
Pow!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Awww... Awww... Awww...
Africa
Wahoo!
Yes, Animals!
Baseball
Roller Coaster
Musical
You've got a lot of hands on you.
Hey, wait! This was really harder than I thought it would be!
Harder in a different way.
No, no, no.
It's just really, really different, and it's been on for a while by itself.
My hands are moving.
No, really.
It's so funny.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry about that.
You got one.
Just one.
It's a little bit really hard.
You'd better be prepared.
Okay.
I'll do it this way.I should have done it this way.
I didn't expect anyone to be in such a tough game.
The first question is on the station platform.
He left shortly after.
He talks so much.
Everyone looked at me like the staff had just started talking.
They looked at me like I was talking.
It really happened unconsciously.
I see.
That's scary.
He could do it.
And then the zoo.
I think I hit it right on the head.
They knew exactly what they were doing.
And then baseball.
He's like, "Oh, I got this." He's like, "Oh, baseball.
Like, "Oh, that's the game from last time.
Next one's live.
I see.
That's what I thought.
I made a mistake.
I almost said "Lupin" and called him by name.
Oh, no!
But you can't do that.
You're supposed to say "Guyon.
It's hard.
Surprisingly.
I mean, it's really hard.
The subject is...
I see.
It sure looks more difficult than before!
Okay, let's start!
Very, very, very, very...
Human
Oh, Coke!
Red Bull
Hey!
Oh, it's a little bit small
Poppin'.
clang
Clang, clang, clang.
Clatter. Kusudama.
What is it?
Wait, wait, wait!
Money, money, money...
Boom, boom, boom. Money box.
Boom!
Gata. Arrangement.
What is it?
Wait, no.
I don't know what to do.
Clang, clang, clang.
There we go. There we go.
Gugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugugu.
What the hell?
Whoa! No!
That's right.
You're good.
Genius. Genius.Genius. Genius.
I've been hit! I've been hit! I've been hit!
Ah, potan
Whoo!
Uh-oh.
Okay, then.
Wait there.
Wait.
It's too hard.
Wait, wait, wait.
Clue moment.
Two seconds.
Surprise!
Too long.
Say you're going to buy a drink of your choice and you're going to drink it.
To the point where you buy it and drink it.
Vending machine
You were really good at that.
The moment he understood, he was all...
He's so complimentary.
That's so sweet.
And the second question was about hot springs.
That's great.
Nice way of putting it.
You started singing.
It's a hot spring, isn't it?
Onsen was hard.
Hot springs...
There's a theme.
It's all the subject's fault.
It's the subject's fault.
You've got to be a little stronger again.
Practice.
We're with you.
You want to do it at night at the ranch?
That's right.
Visitors.
Whatever you do, it's on your own.
It's gonna be a disaster.
I'm going to practice again.
So...
I've been doing ASMR.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
I like this a lot.
It's surprisingly difficult, but it was fun.
Let's practice!
I want to practice at home when I get home with my mom.
Next time, be really strong!
I won't lose!
I'd like to answer your question.
Next time we'll try a different game.
I hope you enjoy it.
Your opponents so far are
Nitruna and
Kinuiaika from the new world.
Bye bye!